(Penny:)than every
single day of my life?
(Sheldon:)I won't be there.
Look at that, it is a party.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Howard:)Sorry I have to work
all weekend.
(Penny:)It's okay.
(Howard:)Thanks again for breakfast.
(Raj:)Well, I didn't get to
see you last night.
(Raj:)It was the least I could do.
(Bernadette:)You shouldn't have made
the alarm code his birthday.
(Raj:)So, what should we do today?
(Bernadette:)Oh, I appreciate it,
(Bernadette:)but you don't have to
spend your day off with me.
(Raj:)Well, I don't mind.
(Raj:)Oh, you want go to the mall
and look at baby stuff?
(Bernadette:)Not really.
(Raj:)Oh, come on,
we could share a pretzel
(Raj:)and get sideways glances
from racist old ladies.
(Bernadette:)I get enough of that
when I take Howard
(Bernadette:)to my grandmother's
for Christmas.
(Sheldon:)Oh,
(Raj:)I know, why don't we get started
on clearing out the baby's room?
(Bernadette:)Isn't it
a little early for that?
(Raj:)You have to
get to it eventually.
(Bernadette:)Oh, there's so much junk
in there, it's embarrassing.
(Raj:)How can you be
embarrassed around me?
(Raj:)I'm gonna be in the room
with you when you give birth.